

CONTACT

- 19, Adebiyi Street, Shomolu, Lagos, Nigeria.
- fasesinolayiwolamathe w@gmail.com
- 08146289500
- in http://linkedin.com/in/m athew-fasesinbb0b66186

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly creative and multi-talented Graphic Designer with extensive experience in multimedia, marketing and print design. To work with passion, sincerity and diligence for the improvement of the organization in a position which will effectively and efficiently display my transferrable skills (graphics design, set design, project management and consultancy (Building and housing construction) and also meet set target, improve and impact society positively.

TECH SKILLS

- CorelDraw
- Photoshop
- Power Point
- Microsoft Word
- Canva
- Affter Effect

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Language: Fluent in English and Yoruba
- Leadership
- High level of Integrity and Discipline
- Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Proactive and goal oriented,
- Project Management (Building)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphics Designer/ Video Editor VOP 90.3FM Airport Ikeja, Lagos

JULY 2022 - PRESENT

- Using the appropriate brand colors and Studying design briefs to determine set requirement layouts for various graphics.
- Working closely with copywriters and creative director to produce the creative concepts for final design.
- Design graphics across various media platforms.
- Edit Videos shot for uploading on YouTube and other Social media channels.
- To Ensure final graphics and layouts are visually appealing and on-brand.
- Making Competitive analysis and making sure to create content according to the latest market trends.
- Contributed to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.

Graphics Executor Rave TV, Ilupeju, Lagos

JUNE 2019- MAY 2022

- Successfully manage and coordinate graphic design and different shows set design projects from concept through completion.
- Work closely with company's mission to create vision, conceive ideas/designs, and consistently meet deadlines and requirements.
- Effectively build, motivate, and direct design and creative
- Design proposals for highly persuasive sales and marketing presentations.
- Successfully created a trademark for the brand.
- Provide layouts and templates for programs.
- Establish relationships with other media firm designers

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

B.A (Theatre Arts and Music)

Lagos State University, Ojo.

2008 - 2014

Senior School Certificate Examination

LillyFields Comprehensive College, Ejigbo, Lagos

HOBBIES/INTEREST

- TRAVELING/ADVENTURING,
- SOCIAL NETWORKING,
- · READING,
- TECH. HOBBIES (COMPUTING),
- POLITICS.
- ART, MUSIC (PLAYING, LISTENING)
- TEAM SPORTS (FOOTBALL)
- HOUSING AND CONSTRUCTION

Graphics Designer, Liberty Prints + Media Institute, Ojo, Lagos.

APRIL 2015 - MARCH 2019

- Completed and maintained accurate records or reports regarding the operations progress of the company's systems.
- Coordinated graphics design project

Large Format and Monogram Operator, Harrymade Prints, Abraham Adesanya Complex, Shomolu, Lagos.

JULY-DECEMBER 2014

- Printed and made copies of work.
- Performed routine maintenance and repairs on printing machines.
- Attended special training sessions to increase knowledge and skills.
- Inspected samples at random during prints runs to identify any errors.
- Responsible for the safe and confidential handling of client's work.
- Ensured machine prints meet the highest quality expectations of clients.

Clerk,

Tunde Bright Enterprises, Shomolu, Lagos.

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JUNE 2012

- Archived complete documents on computer hard drive or disk, and/or maintained a computer filing system to store, retrieve, update and delete documents.
- Printed and made copies of work.
- Manually collated pages of reports and other documents prepared.

A C H I E V E M E N T S / C E R T I F I C A T I O N S

- RaveTV Staff of the Quarter 2020-2021
- Lagos State Readysetwork 2018 (Scholar)
- DigifyNG 2018 (digital marketing skills)
- Students representative for digifyng in LASU (Ambassador)
- Faculty of Arts @ 25 2018 (Organizing Chairman)
- Nigerian Universities Theatre Arts Festival 2017 (Association international des-critiques de theatre international association of theatre critics certification)
- British Council Theatre Festival 2017 (Marketer)
- Faculty of Arts Students Association (Entrepreneur of the Year 2017 & 2018)
- Faculty of Arts Students Association (P. R. O 2017)
- Association of Theatre Arts Students, Lagos State University (Assistant P. R. O 2016)